HENG NIU

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL VALUE

A good attitude is always leading to success. I strongly believe kind is one of the most important personalities to be a successful business entrepreneur as we are always being with human beings. My ethic in business life is kind. I am doing my best to carry out a plan into a reality with my hard work and passion.

I am good at Math, especially fuzzy, geometry, spline, functional analysis and optimization theory.

And I have experienced to perform several artificial intelligence tasks such as error model creating by using BP neural network.

And also I am proficient with image processing and camera calibration using OpenCV.

SKILLS

Primary based languages:

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Node.js, Express.js
- React.js, Angular.js
- MongoDB

Other languages:

- VC++, VB, VC#
- Matlab
- OpenCV

WORK EXPERIENCE

UPPER-LEVEL AND LOWER-LEVEL PROGRAMMING USING C, NUMERICAL CONTROL AND ROBOT CELL 2017-2020

Responsibilities:

- Developing driver for processing events, signals, calculating motion profiles in servo table by using Visual C
- Making user interface, communicating with devices, calibrate and process camera input images by using MFC.
- Data communicating between different devices by using Visual Basic and VC#.

SINGLE APPLICATION AND WEB PROGRAM DEVELOPER 2021-2023

Accomplishments:

- An application for salesman in department store, he/she can easily do tasks such as registering, payment, report by using VC# and MvSOL.
- Develop a program to input a lot of state values and display them onto LCD of a furnace by using VC.
- Responsive Web Design using HTML5, CSS3, javaScript

PERSONAL DETAILS

4594 – Fleming Way. Flagstaff, AZ 23831

T (123) 456 7899 M 000 000 000

hengniudev@hotmail.com

LANGUAGES

English

Advanced: speaking, reading Intermediate: writing

Chinese

Advanced: reading Intermediate: writing

Germany

Basic: writing, reading

REFERENCES

Chuan-Dev Group AlinPop live:sea-technology @hotmail.com Full-Stack programming: Front-End using React.js and Back-End using Express.js and MongoDB

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Beijing University — 2015-2020

IT/Computer Science Faculty

DOCTORAL COURSE IN UNIVERSITY

Beijing University — 2020-2022

IT/Computer Science Faculty